<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
     xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd"
     xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <channel>
    <title>Blue Lightning AI Daily</title>
    <link>https://yourdomain.com/podcast</link>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© 2025 Blue Lightning</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 18:51:43 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    <category>Tech News</category>
    <generator>n8n RSS Builder</generator>
    <description>
      Blue Lightning AI Daily is your go-to AI podcast for creators, delivering fast, focused updates on the world of generative AI. 
      We cover the latest breakthroughs in large language models (LLMs), AI video editing, AI photography, AI audio tools, and creative automation. 
      Each episode gives digital creators, content marketers, and creative professionals clear insights into how AI is transforming storytelling, 
      production, and the creator economy. Stay informed, stay creative, and stay ahead with daily AI news made simple.
    </description>

    <!-- iTunes / Apple Podcasts tags -->
    <itunes:author>Blue Lightning</itunes:author>
    <itunes:summary>
      Blue Lightning AI Daily is your go-to AI podcast for creators, delivering fast, focused updates on the world of generative AI. 
      We cover the latest breakthroughs in LLMs, AI video, AI audio, and creative tools.
    </itunes:summary>
    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    <itunes:image href="https://yourdomain.com/podcast-cover.jpg"/>
    <itunes:owner>
      <itunes:name>Blue Lightning</itunes:name>
      <itunes:email>you@example.com</itunes:email>
    </itunes:owner>

    <!-- Atom self-link (recommended for apps like Apple Podcasts / Overcast) -->
    <atom:link href="https://yourdomain.com/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>

    <!-- Episodes will be inserted here as <item> blocks -->

  
  <item>
    <title>Nano Banana: Google’s Meme Model Delivers Consistent AI Images</title>
    <description><![CDATA[Meet “Nano Banana,” the internet’s favorite new AI image tool from Google Gemini. We break down why creators are buzzing—think stable faces, fast multi-step edits, and watermarked trust. From product colorways to character sheets, find out how Nano Banana makes series-ready visuals a breeze. Plus: pricing, how to try it, and how it stacks up against Midjourney and Firefly. Go bananas for consistency!]]></description>
    <pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 18:21:49 GMT</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=16cbXNQuHsWHBBacH16dcg3ets0bL6zQp" length="3761760" type="audio/mpeg" />
    <guid isPermaLink="false">bl-1756664509406</guid>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>Nano Banana: Gemini’s Meme Engine Takes Over AI Art</title>
    <description><![CDATA[Discover “Nano Banana”—Google Gemini’s viral, high-consistency image engine creators love. Zane and Pippa break down why this fast, stable tool matters for anyone making portraits, product shots, or creative edits. Hear about pricing, watermarks, real-world workflows, and meme magic. Plus, tips for creators, marketers, and devs chasing series-ready results without headaches. Stay consistent—and a little bananas—with Blue Lightning AI Daily!]]></description>
    <pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 18:51:43 GMT</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1lQ8MZUrnUzKX58id4ryCCk1c1oKKmMrB" length="3761760" type="audio/mpeg" />
    <guid isPermaLink="false">bl-1756666303370</guid>
  </item>
</channel>
</rss>
